

## skills

- HTML
- CSS/SASS
- Javascript
- ReactJS
- e NedelC
- NodeJS
- Wordpress
- Final Cut Pro X
- Adobe Lightroom
- Adobe Photoshop
- AutoCAD
- Photography
- Knitting hats

#### interests

- Travel
- Snowboarding
- Rock-climbing
- Being with interesting people
- Being by myself

#### education

- New York Code + Design Academy
  (Intensive Full Stack Web Development 240 hours) 2017
- SAE Auckland (Digital Film Making Diploma ) 2012-2013
- University of Auckland (Bachelor of Arts, English and Sociology)
   2009-2012

+31 6 5414 9672 fran.coulibaly@gmail.com github.com/FranCoulibaly

Gillis van Ledenberchstraat 128/3 Amsterdam 1052VL, NL

# Francesca Coulibaly

## front-end developer

### about me

My broad experience has resulted in a diverse skill set and holistic approach to challenges. The combination of creativity, problem solving and tech, drew me to web development, and my passion for the sector continues to grow.

I am driven by creating aesthetically pleasing and highly functional web applications that engage the user. Curious and ambitious, I am best fitted in a challenging and creative environment.

## work experience

# Front-end Developer Intern - Atelier SAI, Amsterdam, NL. Feb 2018 - present

Developing and maintaining new and existing sites, brand identity tools, e-commerce sites and splash pages. Tech discovery for Al applications. Tools used: Javascript, Wordpress, Greensock (animation library). Clients include ALU, HACKA, Nike and Vossi.

# Co-Producer - African Film Festival NZ, Auckland, NZ. Mar 2014 - Feb 2018

Collaborating with international film makers, distributors and festivals to produce and project manage New Zealand's first African film festival as part of the founding team.

# Assistant Draughtsman - CBA Consultants Ltd, Auckland, NZ. Mar 2013 - Jul 2016

Designed and drew civil engineering technical drawings using AutoCAD and wrote town planning reports. Clients included local councils, international property developers and private landowners.

### • Freelance film making, NZ. Oct 2012 – May 2015

Production/director/editing assistant and full creative control on a number of productions. Clients included BBC, Converse NZ, Waterfront Auckland, Auckland Live and local musicians and artists.

# Production Assistant / Editing Assistant - Bayly & Moore, Auckland, NZ. June 2011 - Mar 2013

Used Final Cut Pro X and Lightroom, often utilising After Effects and Photoshop.